A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Transportation, 1977-1985
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Transportation, 1977-1985
The Library of Virginia
32591
19 cu. ft.
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Transportation
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred by the Office of the Secretary of Transportation, 19 December 1985.
Custodial History
This collection was transferred by the Secretary of Transportation and Public Saftey, but the contents were collected durring a transition period and encompas both Secretary of Transoprtation and Secretary of Transporation and Public Safety Records. The collection has been filed under the Secretary of Transportation because the bulk of materials are relative to transportation.
Biographical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governors top management team or "secretariats," as they are called now.
Governor Linwood Holton's top priority for the 1972 session of the General Assembly was a proposal for a Governor's Cabinet, reorganizing state agencies into six major departments--each headed by a secretary appointed by the governor. Transportation and public safety was one of these six departments. The office of Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was created on April 8, 1972, by an act passed by the General Assembly. Governor Holton appointed Wayne A. Whitham, a member of the Winchester City Council, as the first Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety. When Whitham took office on July 1, 1972, he was responsible for State Highway Commission, Division of Motor Vehicles, Department of State Police, Highway Safety Division, Office of Emergency Services, Department of Military Affairs, Virginia State Crime Commission and the Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission. The Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations since. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature established separate secretariats for transportation and for public safety, effective July 1, 1976. On July 1, 1984, the offices were again combined. Most recently, the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was divided into separate secretariats on February 22, 1990. The Secretary of Transportation is a member of the Governor's Cabinet, and is appointed by the governor, subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. The Secretary is responsible to the governor for the Department of Transportation, Department of Rail and Public Transportation, Department of Aviation, Department of Motor Vehicles, Virginia Port Authority and the Motor Vehicle Dealers Board.
Wayne A. Whitham, the first Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, was reappointed by Governor-elect Miles E. Godwin, Jr., in December 1973 and by Governor-elect John N. Dalton in December 1977. Whitham suffered a heart attack in August 1978 and resigned in December 1978. On June 7, 1984, Whitham died in Richmond, Virginia. Governor Dalton named George M. Walters, a former top executive of the Reynolds Metals Corporation, to succeed Whitham as Secretary of Transportation. Walters served until the end of Dalton's term in January 1982. Governor-elect Charles S. Robb, the first Democrat to be elected governor since 1965, did not retain any of Dalton's cabinet secretaries. Robb appointed Andrew B. Fogarty, Dalton's assistant secretary for financial policy, as Secretary of Transportation. On July 1, 1984, the secretariats of transportation and public safety were combined again. As a result this partial reorganization of state government, Governor Robb appointed Fogarty Secretary of Administration and Franklin E. White, Secretary of Public Safety, assumed Fogarty's Transportation duties. White, who served as a White House liaison official under President Jimmy Carter, resigned in June 1985 to become the New York state commissioner of transportation. He was replaced by Andrew Fogarty who served until the end of the Robb administration. He later served as Governor Gerald L. Baliles chief of staff from August 1986 to October 1989 when he resigned to become a vice president with CSX Corporation.
In December 1985, Governor-elect Gerald L. Baliles, picked Vivian E. Watts, a northern Virginia legislator, as Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety. Watts served until the end of Baliles' term in 1990. In 1995 she was elected to her old seat in the Virginia House of Delegates. On February 22, 1990, the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was divided into separate secretariats. Governor L. Douglas Wilder, appointed John G. Milliken, a member of the Arlington County Board of Supervisors, as the Secretary of Transportation. Milliken resigned on December 17, 1993.
In February 1994 Governor George Allen, the first Republican elected governor since 1977, appointed Robert Martinez as Secretary of Transportation. Martinez was born in Cuba and had served as Deputy Administrator for the Marine Administration and Associate Deputy Secretary of Transportation during President George H.W. Bush's administration. At the end of Governor Allen's term in January 1998, Martinez joined the Norfolk Southern Corporation. Shirley Ybarra, deputy Secretary of Transportation in the Allen administration, was named Martinez's successor by Governor-elect James Gilmore. Ybarra previously worked as a special assistant to Transportation Secretary Elizabeth Dole during President Ronald Reagan's administration. Ybarra served until the end of Gilmore's administration in January 2002. Whittington W. Clement, a former lawyer and long-time member of the Virginia House of Delegates representing the City of Danville, was appointed Secretary of Transportation by Governor Mark R. Warner in 2002. Pierce R. Homer, Deputy Secretary of Transportation, replaced Clement in 2005.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of files relating to Virginia's highways, roads, ports, rail lines, and airports. Correspondents include the Governor's Office, Department of Motor Vehicles, Department of Corrections and Office of Emergency Services. There is also correspondence with U.S. Representative Frank R. Wolf (R - 10th District) conserning a Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority and a stop as far south as Springfield, Virginia.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1977-1985., Extent: 19 cu. ft. (19 boxes). (Box 1-19)
  This collection maintains the agency's original filing order, the first ten boxes are arranged alphabetically (generally) and the following nine are arranged by corresondant.
  - AMTRAK, 1982-1983. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Augusta County, 19843. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Buchanan County, 1982-1983. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget Information, 1982-1984. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cape Charles, 1980-1982. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CARES Program, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CARES Program, 1982. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Carter-Goble Consultant, 1982. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cetral Garage Car Pool Committee, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel, 1977-1983. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Coal: Exporting, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Coal: Parsons Brinckerhoff - Loading Facility, 1981-1982. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Coal: Slurry, 1982-1983. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Conferences/Meetings, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1982-1983. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Crime Commission, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Consultants, 1980-1982. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Crime Prevention, 1982-1983. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Delmarva, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dredging: Hampton Roads Harbor, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dredging: Port Authority (House Resolution 5073), 1982. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Drug Plan, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Drunk Driving, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dulles Access Road, 1978-1983. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dulles Access Toll Road: Public Hearing, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dulles International Airport: Acquisition Study Commission, 1977-1981. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dulles Airport, 1982. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dulles Policy Task Force, 1982-1983. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dulles Policy Task Force, 1980-1981. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Shore Rail Service, 1979-1982. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Shore Railroad: Escrow/Loan Agreement, 1980. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Equal Employment Oppertunity, 1981-1983. (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - Executive Agreements, 1983. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Federal: Emergency Management, 1982-1983. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Federal: Highway Administration, 1982-1984. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Federal: Railroad Administration, 1981-1983. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Federal: Transportation Safety Board, 1983. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Financial Aid to Localities, 1983. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1980-1983. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Governor Charles S. Robb: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Office: General, 1983. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hampton Police Union, 1983. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Handicapped and Elderly, 1983-1984. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Henrico/Arlington Funding, 1982-1984. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Human Resources Transportation Study, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Highways and Interstates: I-66-Congressman Parris, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Highways and Interstates: I-66-Lynn Street Ramp, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Highways and Interstates: I-66-Warner, Wolf, Trible, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Highways and Interstates: I-66-Rosslynn Plaza, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Highways and Interstates: I-395-Ramp Metering, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Highways and Interstates: Route 1-4 year Trail/Potomac High School, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Highways and Interstates: Route 28 - Prince William/Manassas, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Highways and Interstates: Route 50 - Arlington County, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Highways and Interstates: Route 642 - Bridge-Cape Charles, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Highways and Interstates: Bluefield Bypass/Route 460, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Highways and Interstates: Laburnum/Chippenham Connector, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Highways and Interstates: Lee Bridge (Richmond City), 1982. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Highways and Interstates: Manassas Bypass/Route 234, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Highways and Interstates: Memorial Drive (NOVA), 1983. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Highways and Interstates: North Kings Highway/Fairfax County, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Highways and Interstates: Skyline Center/George Mason Drive, 1981-1983. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Highways and Interstates: South Pantops Drive/Charlottesville, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Highways and Interstates: Wagner and Wells Road (Sisisky), 1983. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Highways and Interstates: Williams Viaduct, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - International Trade and Marketing, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Invoices, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Invoices, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Joint Legislative Audit Review Commission, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Joint Legislative Audit Review Commission: Exposure Draft, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Joint Legislative Audit Review Commission: Manpower Study, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Joint Legislative Audit Review Commission: Highways and Transportation - Study (SJR 50), 1980. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: General, 1982-1983. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Session, 1984. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: House Bill 532 - Gas Tax, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Legislation: House Joint Resolution 34, 1982-1983. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Senate Joint Resolution 10, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Senate Bill 304, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Load Shifting, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan: Planning Organization, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan: Stable and Reliable (WMATA), 1981-1982. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan: General Information, 1982-1985. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan: Compact/Agreement, 1984-1985. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan: Conlan, John T. - Tysons Corner Project, 1982-1984. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan: Rail, 1982-1984. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - minority Information and Office of Minority Business Affairs, 1981-1983. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Modified Vehicle Suspension System, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Montgomery County Community Sentencing Program, 1982-1983. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Moving and Relocation Regulations, 1983-1984. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - National Association of State Aviation Officials, 1982. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - National Governor's Association, 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Governor's Association, 1984. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - National Governor's Association: Committee on Transportation - Commerce and Technology (General Information), 1983-1984. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - National Governor's Association: Staff Advisory Council, 1985 June 6. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - National Institute of Corrections - Jail Center, 1982. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Neighborhood Watch in Virginia, 1983. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - News Media, 1983. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Non-Violent Offenders, 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Norfolk-Southern Railroad, 1983. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission, 1981-1983. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Offender Aid and Resoration, 1981-1983. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Office of Minority Business Affairs: VSOMBE Consulting Contractor, 1982-1983. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Office of Minority Business Affairs: Anderson, Gerard A., 1982. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Office of Minority Business Affairs: Highway Component, 1982 Oct 1. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Office of Minority Business Affairs: Memorandum of Understanding (Special Provisions), 1983. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Office of Minority Business Affairs: Minority Business Task Force (Ron Johnson Contract), 1983. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Office of Minority Business Affairs: STAA Congressional Hearing, 1983 Sept 2. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Oil Recycling Program, 1982-1983. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Outreach Counceling Services, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Personnel and Training: General, 1982-1983. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Personnel: Ceiling and 5 percent cut, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Planning and Budget: General, 1981-1982. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Police Association, Virginia Chiefs of, 1982-1983. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Property: State Owned, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Public Transportation, State Financing Study, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Railroads/Rail Transportation, 1981-1982. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Reimbursment to Localities, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Restitution Program, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Retrocession: Norfolk - Navy, 1977-1983. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company (RF&P), 1981-1983. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Risk Assessment Task Force, 1983. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ridesharing, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Science and Technology: Task Force, 1983. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1983. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Supreme Court of Virginia, 1981;1983. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Telecommunications, Division of, 1982-1983. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Title XX, 1982-1983. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Truckers Associations, 1983. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Truck Enforcement Program, 1981-1983. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Trucks: Legal/Civil Action, 1983. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Trucks: Load Shifting, 1982. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Trucks: Weight (House Bill 749), 1983. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Truck Weight Enforcement, 1982-1983. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Trucks Weights and Sizes, 1978-1983. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Trucks Weights and Sizes: Virginia Directives, Executive Orders, and Legislation, 1977-1982. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Twin Trailers, 1983. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ultrasystems, Inc., 1981-1983. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - United Airlines, 1982. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - United Bio-Fuel Industries, Inc., 1981-1982. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - United Coal Company, 1983. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation - Secretary of Transportation, 1981-1982. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Urban Mass Transportation Administration, 1981-1983. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Bar Association, 1982. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1980-1984. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Judicial Conference, 1981-1983. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Municipal League, 1981-1983. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Visually Handicapped, 1979-1981. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Washington National Airport, 1981-1982. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - World Trade Center, 1981. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - WEL Conference, 1982. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Wolf Trap, 1983. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Department of Highways and Transportation - Misc., 1983. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Level Funding, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Level Funding, 1984-1986. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Transportation - Financial Information, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Transportation - Financial Information, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Transportation - Employee Levels, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Transportation - Financial Study of Transportation Agencies, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of transportation - Level Funding, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Transportation - Accomplishments, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Department of Aviation - Air Service Development Division, 1981-1983. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Department of Aviation - Airport and Airway Development Act, 1975-1983. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Department of Aviation - Commercial Air Travel Study, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Department of Aviation - Commuter Slots Passenger Capacity, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Department of Aviation - Chesterfield Airport Extension, 1982. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Department of Aviation - General, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Department of Aviation - Gray, James H., 1982. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Department of Aviation - IPA Transfers, 1982-1983. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Department of Aviation - Federal Aviation Administration: Scatter Plam, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Office of Emergency and Energy Services - Conservation Program, 1981-1983. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Office of Emergency Services - General, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Office of Emergency Services - General, 1981-1982. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Energy Policy Task Force, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Exceptional Action Requests, 1981. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Fuel Allocation Program, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Mutual Support Agreement and Designation of Authority, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Metropolitan Washington Emergency Preparedness, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Disaster Costs Sharing by Local, State and Federal, 1983. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Nuwax, 1983. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Office of Emergency Services - Solar Energy and Conservation Bank, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Department of Fire Programs - General, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Department of Fire Programs - General, 1982. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Commission, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Commuter Rail Study Northern Virginia, 1982. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Fairfax County, 1983. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - General, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Highway Allocation Formula (Senate Joint Resolution 20), 1983. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Prision Productivity Study with Public Safety, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Public Transportation, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Research Council: Charlottesville, 1982-1983. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Road Problems, 1983. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Department of Highways and Transportation - Joint Legislative Audit Review Commission on Maintenance Funding, 1984. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Armories: Construction and Maintenance, 1983. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Employers Support of the Guard, 1983-1984. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Department of Military Affairs - General, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Meeting with Secretary of the Army, 1982 Nov 30. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Department of Military Affairs - State Police: Surpressing Drug Trafficking, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Virginia Military Institute Scholarship, 1983. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Branch Offices, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Child Restraints and Safety Seat Programs, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Driver Improvement Program, 1982. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - General, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Maintenance and Construction Fund, 1981-1983. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Governor's Task Force on Drunk Driving, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Merger, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Conferences, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Sheriffs Suspension Orders, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - Unprotected Railroad Crossing: Operation Lifesaver, 1979-1983. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Department of Motor Vehicles - VASAP Program, 1982-1983. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Virignia Port Authority - General, 1983. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Virignia Port Authority - CSX Land Acquistion: Newport News, 1983. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Board of Commissions, 1983. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Audits/Financial, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Deep Draft Navigation Act, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Labor, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Virignia Port Authority - World Trade Center, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Polish Ocean Lines, 1984. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Remarks for the Governor, 1982-1983. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Security Force, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Skinner, Aluster C.: Longshoreman, 1979-1983. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Virignia Port Authority - User Fee Financing, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Port Unification: Portsmouth Marine Terminal, 1982-1983. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Task Force to Study Alternatives for Rail Access to Portsmouth, 1982. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Water Resources Sub-Committee Hearings, 1982. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Conflict of Interest Disclosure Forms, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 13)